♪I woke up in a strange place♪
♪The sunlight here is blindingly bright♪
♪Pages rustle, and I hear a loud voice♪
♪I've become the center of the story♪
♪I must escape this dream♪
♪Yet why does my heart
surrender before you♪
♪Clearly, it's a fake plot♪
♪A fake world♪
♪Yet eventually,
my heart is open to you♪
=My Page in the 90s=
(Adapted from "Bye, Wild Weasel")
=Episode 24=
Let's do a quick survey.
Sure.
On weekends, do you prefer
climbing mountain or sleeping in?
Sleeping in on the mountain.
Okay.
For anniversary,
do you prefer a handwritten love letter
or a romantic trip for two?
During the romantic trip for two,
you give me a love letter.
Okay. Then do you prefer walking
with an umbrella on rainy days
or biking on sunny days?
You ride the motorcycle with me on it,
and I hold the umbrella.
Rain or shine,
nothing stops us.
I didn't expect you to be so greedy.
It's too late for you to know that now.
These wontons are so delicious.
What if I can't eat them in the future?
Just a moment.
What's wrong?
Sir, Mr. Jin.
I'd like to learn
how to make wontons from you.
Please teach me the secret recipe,
so I can make it for my girlfriend.
Okay, sure.
- Okay. Come on.
- Okay.
- I'll teach you.
- Thank you.
Look, just like this.
♪Old times, pass slowly♪
♪In memories, the breeze is soft♪
♪Your smile is shimmering like stars♪
♪Lighting up my lonely corner♪
♪Love's time machine,
flies, flies, flies♪
(Wonton Recipe)
♪Through centuries, just to meet you♪
♪Love's time machine keeps on turning♪
♪Streaking across the sky♪
♪Just to hold you♪
♪Old times, pass slowly♪
♪In memories, the breeze is soft♪
Try it.
I made it myself.
This has gone cold.
Careful, it's hot.
How is it?
Delicious?
Why does it taste exactly the same
as Mr. Jin's?
Seems like I've succeeded.
This wonton place
looks ordinary,
and with nothing special.
Why is their food so delicious?
Any secret recipe?
This is the recipe.
But you can't read it now.
Read it when the time comes.
Here, keep it.
Remember
when we had wonton for the first time,
you hired someone
to secretly take photos of us
and pretended to wipe my mouth?
I've kept that magazine.
Gao Haiming.
Actually, before I met you,
I couldn't understand
people in love at all.
They seemed so retarded.
Just because they did some boring
trivial things together,
they would giggle like fools
when thinking of them.
But now, whenever I think
of the time I spent with you,
I'd do the same.
All the memories we have together
are all in my mind.
Even if we never see each other again,
I'd have no regret.
What?
Nothing.
I remember
there's an amusement park nearby.
Want to go?
Now? It's too late now, right?
We couldn't play anything then.
If we set off now, we'll make it.
Let's go.
Now?
It's so dark here. How can we play?
Wait for me.
No way.
Does it look like what you mentioned?
What was it called?
Old-style?
Never mind it.
It's so cool.
Which one?
Let's play them all.
Okay, let's go.
What is this?
I always thought amusement parks
were only for kids,
but I didn't expect
to have so much fun here.
Right. It's my first time
at an amusement park.
I'm really happy.
You've never been to an amusement park?
Then you've never ridden a carousel?
No.
You've never ridden a carousel?
How could you?
Would you get dizzy on this?
No.
How could I get dizzy on this?
But if I do feel dizzy,
hold me steady.
When I rode carousels as a kid,
I thought they were slow.
And I wished they'd go much faster.
What about now?
Now...
Now I think slowing down is good.
Slowing down
lets me see clearly those around me
and truly feel this present moment.
I used to make wishes
on carousels as a child.
Make wishes on carousels?
When my parents brought me here,
I'd ride the carousel
and make a wish.
I wish to get a new toy
from my parents the next day,
or to get better in my exams.
Then, any wishes now?
Now,
I wish...
Wait, you need to make wishes sincerely.
Close your eyes.
Huan'er.
Though we've not been together for long,
we've shared many moments
that are unforgettable.
So, will you marry me
and spend your life with me?
But my life...
Huan'er.
Doesn't matter.
Whether it's a lifetime,
a day,
or even one minute, one second,
as long as I'm with you,
that makes my whole life.
Do you?
I...
I do.
Gao Haiming, I do.
♪Entwined worries linger♪
♪My heart is not empty,
yet pain remains♪
♪Now I see what passed between us♪
♪Walking through the crowd to meet you♪
♪Going through surging tides of people♪
♪Until the world's end♪
♪If I could♪
♪Keep loving you♪
♪Hearing two hearts♪
♪Beating together♪
♪If I could♪
♪Stay resting in your arms♪
♪I'd trade the rest of my life for it♪
I love you.
Huan'er.
Huan'er, wake up.
What's wrong, Huan'er?
- Huan'er.
Are you okay?
Are you okay? Too tired?
- What happened?
- Huan'er.
The live stream starts soon.
You need touch-ups.
Huan'er, what's going on?
So,
will you marry me
and spend your life with me?
Gao Haiming, I do.
Huan'er.
Huan'er, what's wrong?
The upcoming live streams are crucial.
We have to win the challenge.
Huan'er!
Has a man named Gao Haiming
come to the company?
There's no such person.
Oh my.
Only fifteen minutes to go.
If we don't go back now,
Mr. Zeng will kill us!
Why is there no such person?
Gao Haiming!
Sanitary pads, no.
Gao Haiming came to our office
to acquire our company.
Don't you remember?
Did I agree to it?
Someone wants to acquire our company?
Who?
Mr. Gao Haiming. Haven't you met him?
Mr. Gao?
I've never heard of
anyone named Gao Haiming.
Mr. Zeng.
Huan'er might not be feeling well today.
Not feeling well?
I think you've lost your mind.
How is that possible?
You scheduled to meet with him.
What's today's date?
February 16th, Huan'er.
You've lost track of time?
(The first time meeting Gao Haiming)
(should be February 28th.)
(Why did I come back to February 16th?)
If you're not feeling well,
you can cancel the live stream.
Understood?
Cancel it.
Impossible.
He has to be in this world.
Huan'er.
Where are you going?
Huan'er!
(Gao Haiming)
(Gao Haiming, not found)
(Xinning South Road)
Sir, go to North Boyang Road first.
Okay.
Excuse me.
Was this area a villa district before?
Right here.
Never heard of it.
Excuse me.
May I ask
if this place was Letao?
A supermarket?
No.
It's fine, thanks.
You are just too fixated
on reaching a destination
and miss the views along the way.
Isn't it an even bigger shame?
You always seem so emotionally stable.
It's not that I'm stable.
You're always in a hurry.
You're in a hurry to find a place,
to solve a problem,
and to finish a task.
Why are you in such a rush?
Sometimes, wasting time
can be a kind of joy too.
Try it.
♪My heart is pounding♪
♪Old times, pass slowly♪.
♪In memories, the breeze is soft♪
♪Your smile is shimmering like stars♪
♪Lighting up my lonely corner♪.
♪Love's time machine,
flies, flies, flies♪
♪Through centuries, just to meet you♪.
♪Love's time machine keeps on turning♪.
♪Streaking across the sky♪.
I'll double-check with Huan'er.
Okay.
I wonder if she will live stream today.
You're finally back.
You've been looking for Gao Haiming.
He's a character in a book.
You won't find him.
Xiaoyu.
Let me tell you.
Here in our world,
there must be a Gao Haiming.
And I will find him.
Huan'er, are you going to live stream
today?
Yes.
Really?
Perfect!
I'll go prepare.
(Hello, I am back!)
It's been a while.
How have you been?
(Ai Qing)
(Ai Qing requests to join)
(Tonight, we're talking about love.)
Lin Huan'er, are you ready?
Yes, let's just start.
You sound
so confident while talking big.
I didn't understand it before.
I thought love wasn't
anything important.
And I never believed
that there could be
someone in this world
who gives it all to another
without asking rewards.
We should be independent in life.
We should live for ourselves.
Thinking back now,
I was too assertive.
Actually, a proper love relationship
makes you gentler
and stronger.
Love is all about who you are,
not what I wish.
Huan'er seems different.
Huan'er, being so idealistic
will get you hurt.
Sweeties,
you must distinguish
between romance novels and reality.
After reading
romance novels,
many people pursue romantic love.
Those romantic plots
make you yearn for love.
But love in reality?
Those are toxic,
will only let you be devoured by men.
I once had an unforgettable love.
That man...
How to put it?
He was a man from the last century,
very old-style.
At the very beginning,
I used every trick
from 2025 to win him over,
but they all failed.
Until one day,
I gave up the tricks,
and started being sincere.
That's when I won his love.
Every second we spent together
was blissful.
He took me to experience
all the cliché plots
from old-style romance novels.
But thinking back now,
I realize I actually loved them.
We can't see each other now,
and we're not even
in the same time or space,
but I still believe
his love will always be there.
So, true love
comes when an unwavering heart
meets another unwavering heart.
(Monitor the house at a glance,
Control as you wish)
Master, you're back.
Today's weather is sunny to cloudy.
Temperature is 19 to 22 degrees Celsius.
How are you feeling today?
What should I play for you?
What would you like for dinner?
Let me suggest some recipes.
Handmade Wontons.
Sweet and Sour Ribs.
Crab Roe Tofu.
Pine Nut Corn.
(This is the only thing
brought back from that world.)
(This is the recipe.)
(But you can't read it now.)
Read it when the time comes.
Here, keep it.
♪My heart is not empty,
yet pain remains♪
(Huan'er.)
(You came into my world,)
(giving me joy and love
I'd never known before.)
(Don't be sad. Life is long.)
(It's worth spending a lifetime)
(proving your love for someone.)
(No matter where or when you are,)
(I'll go to your world this time,)
(to get to you.)
♪Hearing two hearts♪
♪Beating together♪
♪If I could♪
♪Stay resting in your arms♪
(Wonton Recipe)
♪Entwined worries linger♪
Try it. I made it myself.
♪Now I see what passed between us♪
♪Walking through the crowd to meet you♪
♪Going through surging tides of people♪
♪Until the world's end♪
♪If I could♪
♪Keep loving you♪
♪Hearing two hearts♪
♪Beating together♪
♪If I could♪
♪Stay resting in your arms♪
♪I'd trade the rest of my life for it♪
Gao Haiming.
You must remember me.
Happy?
Me too.
Super happy.
Where should we go?
Let's go see.
What do you want to play?
Want some marshmallow?
Yes.
I'll go buy some.
Wait here.
Okay.
♪Entwined worries linger♪
♪My heart is not empty,
yet pain remains♪
♪Now I see what passed between us♪
♪Walking through the crowd to meet you♪
♪Going through surging tides of people♪
(Gao Haiming.)
(You must remember me.)
♪If I could♪
(Forget it.)
(You should just forget about me.)
♪Beating together♪
♪If I could♪
♪Stay resting in your arms♪
♪I'd trade the rest of my life for it♪
♪Entwined worries linger♪
♪My heart is not empty,
yet pain remains♪
(Gao Haiming, where are you?)
♪Walking through the crowd to meet you♪
♪Going through surging tides of people♪
♪Until the world's end♪
♪If I could♪
♪Keep loving you♪
♪Hearing two hearts♪
♪Beating together♪
♪If I could♪
♪Stay resting in your arms♪
♪I'd trade the rest of my life for it♪
(Huan'er, I will go to you.)
(No matter where you go,)
(whenever you need me,)
(I'll go to you.)
Huan'er, well done.
Okay, thanks.
Thank you.
Huan'er.
A package for you.
It's huge.
I'll get back to work.
Okay, thanks.
(From Mr. Gao)
(Xinning South Road)
Sorry.
♪Timelines, tangled♪
♪I boarded a rickety time machine♪
♪My heart is pounding♪
♪Old times, pass slowly♪
♪In memories, the breeze is soft♪
♪Your smile is shimmering like stars♪
♪Lighting up my lonely corner♪
♪Love's time machine,
flies, flies, flies♪
♪Through centuries, just to meet you♪
♪Love's time machine keeps on turning♪
♪Streaking across the sky♪
♪Just to hold you♪
♪Old photos, yellowed♪
♪Timelines, tangled♪
♪I boarded a rickety time machine♪
♪My heart is pounding♪
♪Old times, pass slowly♪
♪In memories, the breeze is soft♪
♪Your smile is shimmering like stars♪
♪Lighting up my lonely corner♪
♪Love's time machine,
flies, flies, flies♪
♪Through centuries, just to meet you♪
♪Love's time machine keeps on turning♪
(Capricorn)
Why is one missing here?
Capricorn.
While I don't understand models,
I completely understand that feeling
of wanting
to complete a whole collection.
Missing just this one model
does feel slightly imperfect.
I used to think so too.
But now I believe
imperfection leaves room
for anticipation, doesn't it?
Makes sense.
(Happy birthday, Huan'er)
♪Entwined worries linger♪
♪My heart is not empty,
yet pain remains♪
♪Now I see what passed between us♪
♪Walking through the crowd to meet you♪
♪Going through surging tides of people♪
♪Until the world's end♪
♪If I could♪
♪Keep loving you♪
♪Hearing two hearts♪
♪Beating together♪
♪If I could♪
♪Stay resting in your arms♪
♪I'd trade the rest of my life for it♪
♪Entwined worries linger♪
♪My heart is not empty,
yet pain remains♪
♪Now I see what passed between us♪
Long time no see.
♪Going through surging tides of people♪
♪Until the world's end♪
♪If I could♪
♪Keep loving you♪
♪Hearing two hearts♪
♪Beating together♪
♪If I could♪
♪Stay resting in your arms♪
♪I'd trade the rest of my life for it♪
♪Entwined worries linger♪
♪My heart is not empty,
yet pain remains♪
♪Now I see what passed between us♪
♪Walking through the crowd to meet you♪
♪Going through surging tides of people♪
♪Until the world's end♪
♪If I could♪
♪Keep loving you♪
♪Hearing two hearts♪
♪Beating together♪
♪If I could♪
♪Stay resting in your arms♪
♪I'd trade the rest of my life for it♪
(Lin Huan'er and Gao Haiming
are kissing passionately.)
(At this moment,
they only see each other.)
(As for how Gao Haiming
came to Lin Huan'er's world,)
(that is another story.)
(Perhaps in his pager system,)
(every step he took toward Lin Huan'er)
(shapes their love story.)
(Because I believe)
(love is the only force
that can transcend space and time.)
(Grateful to see you again.)
♪Entwined worries linger♪
♪My heart is not empty,
yet pain remains♪
♪Now I see what passed between us♪
♪Walking through the crowd to meet you♪
♪Going through surging tides of people♪
♪Until the world's end♪
♪If I could♪
♪Keep loving you♪
♪Hearing two hearts♪
♪Beating together♪
♪If I could♪
♪Stay resting in your arms♪
♪I'd trade the rest of my life for it♪
♪Entwined worries linger♪
♪My heart is not empty,
yet pain remains♪
♪Now I see what passed between us♪
♪Walking through the crowd to meet you♪
♪Going through surging tides of people♪
♪Until the world's end♪
♪If I could♪
♪Keep loving you♪
♪Hearing two hearts♪
♪Beating together♪
♪If I could♪
♪Stay resting in your arms♪
♪I'd trade the rest of my life for it♪